domain.name 2002-12-04

# :: The Global Name Registry, Limited :: Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
The Global Name Registry, Limited ("Global Name Registry") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web Site.

**Personal information**  
We use your IP address to help detect and diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Our site's mailing list form requires users to give us contact information (their name and email address). We may use customer contact information from the mailing list form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. We will not give, sell, rent, loan, or otherwise disclose to any third parties outside of Global Name Registry (and/or its outsourced providers only to the extent necessary for the operation of the registry), except when we have given you notice or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with legal process, (ii) enforce the service terms and conditions, or (iii) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Global Name Registry, its customers, or the public. We may provide prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties with statistics but such provision will be purely generic and never be tied to a specific user. We may use your contact information to contact you when necessary.

The Privacy Policy set out here only relates to the collection and processing of data on the Web site. The privacy policies of our partners (including parties who provide **.name** registration services) may differ from our Privacy Policy, and you should verify the precise terms of the privacy policies of such third parties when assessing their websites before providing any personal information. Please note that, when registering a **.name** , the personal information that you provide at the time of registration will become available on the Whois database and will be accessible by third parties.

**Security**  
At Global Name Registry, security has been put on top of the list from day one. This site has many security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. For users who require added security we will support SSL encryption throughout the whole Global Name Registry website. SSL will provide a secure link between you and our systems that protects against eavesdropping.

**Opt Out**  
From time to time, Global Name Registry may notify **.name** subscribers of new products, announcements, upgrades and updates. Users may opt-out of receiving these future promotional mailings by sending an email with their name to: 

[unsubscribe@gnr.com](mailto:unsubscribe@gnr.com) or by contacting us at our mailing address:

The Global Name Registry, Limited  
5th Floor  
125 High Holborn  
London WC1V 6QA  
England

Global Name Registry reserves the right to send users email related to business practices and systems operations, such as outage notifications and quota warnings, even if the user has opted out of promotional mailings.

Users may also request information on the personal information maintained on them with Global Name Registry by contacting Global Name Registry at the above noted address.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Global Name Registry directly. Please see the "Contact Us" section of the Web site for contact information.
